Today I will see what I can eat at Surat Railway Station
for ₹100.  Right
at the beginning I see Dhokla, the pride of Gujarat.
Now Bapu, this Dhokla is really
amazing brother.  Now I find it so
amazing.  Then I
go to the same shop again and
buy this.  Now I don't even know the name of this pakora like thing.
And it is
not that much fun to eat it.  Meanwhile I
see ice cream on the other platform.
Now I have to wander around a lot to eat this ice cream.
But I don't know where it
disappears.  Then it is also found.  Brother,
ice cream is very good.
But one thing I did not understand was that whatever
I ate here was for ₹30 each.  Now I am
unable to understand what to eat with this remaining ₹10.  You can get
churka-mukuras for ₹10
but you cannot eat them.  I see a brother
carrying a big loaf.  Now
I have never eaten all this at the railway station.   The
brother selling the big pav says that he will not be
able to give it.  I don't know what rule Bhaiya had
that he doesn't give even one big loaf.
Babu, if you want to buy then take two big loaves.  I had that much
budget otherwise I would have refused.
Now what should I do with this huge amount of money that is left
?  You tell